A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- II. Office of the Secretary, 2001-2006., Extent: 14.55 cubic feet (36 boxes). (Box 14, 21-55)
  - Subseries II.A. Records of Secretary Michael J. Schewel, 2001-2006., Extent: 4.85 cubic feet. (Box 14, 21-31)
    - Subject Files
      - Organization of State Government Chart for Fiscal Year 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Strategic Planning, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Governor Warner's Meeting with Silicon Semiconductor, 2 May 2003 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Cabinet Work Group on Budget Development and Governmental Restructuring (Bennett Commmittee), 2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Agency Head Meetings, 2003-2005 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Executive Agreements, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Secretary of Commerce and Trade Initiatives, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Executive Order No. 6, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - State Forester Candidates, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Reports (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Reports (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence-Chronological
      - 12 January 2006-27 September 2005 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - 26 September 2005-6 June 2005 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - 3 June 2005-17 March 2005 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - 14 March 2005-27 December 2004 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - 23 December 2004-27 October 2004 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - 26 October 2004-23 July 2004 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - 22 July 2004-7 June 2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - 1 June 2004-18 March 2004 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 16 March 2004-4 January 2004 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - 30 December 2003-12 November 2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - 10 November 2003-9 September 2003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - 8 September 2003-7 July 2003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - 30 June 2003-25 April 2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 23 April 2003-13 February 2003 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - 12 February 2003-26 November 2002 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - 22 November 2002-30 August 2002 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - 27 August 2002-5 June 2002 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - 30 May 2002-5 April 2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - 4 April 2002-22 January 2002 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Governor's Correspondence, 13 September 2005-8 October 2002 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Governor's Correspondence, 4 October 2002-25 January 2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence-General
      - General Correspondence, 2002 Jan-Feb. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 Mar-Apr. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 May. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 June-July. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 Aug. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 Sept. (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 Oct. (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 Nov. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence, 2002 Dec. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 Jan-Feb. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 Mar-Apr. (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 May. (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 June. (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 July. (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 July. (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 Aug. (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 Sept-Oct. (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - General Correspondence, 2003 Nov-Dec. (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - 12 January 2006-25 August 2005 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - 19 August 2005-4 March 2005 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - 28 February 2005-3 January 2005 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - 28 December 2004-19 October 2004 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - 18 October 2004-3 September 2004 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - 2 September 2004-24 June 2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - 23 June 2004-3 May 2004 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - 30 April 2004-25 March 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - 23 March 2004-11 February 2004 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - 10 February 2004-6 January 2004 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Speeches
      - 2002-2005 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - 2002-2005 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - 2002-2005 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - 2002-2005 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Calendar
      - 2002 Appointment Calendar (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP)
      - Certifications, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Subseries II.B. Records of Deputy Secretary Matt Erskine, 2001-2005., Extent: 8.65 cubic feet. (Box 32-52)
    This subseries is housed in 21 boxes and is divided into 5 sections: Agency and Subject Files, Thank You Notes, Correspondence-Chronological, Special Projects and Events.
    Subjects found in the Agency and Subject Files division include: Virginia's response to the Avian Influenza outbreak in the Commonwealth in 2002 (b32, f2).
    The Thank You Notes division is arranged in chronlogical order and consists of incoming thank you notes to Erskine. The Correspondence-Chronological division consists of copies of Erskine's outgoing correspondence only.
    The Special Projects division is arranged in alphabetical order. Subjects include: Virginia Biotechnology Initiative, Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC), Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC), drought, Virginia Agriculture and Forestry Export Strategy Task Force, Jobs for Virginia initiative, Small Business Initiative, Virginia Tourism, and Virginia Wine Industry.
    Notable documents filed under Special Projects include: report titled "Doubling Net Receipts in Virginia Agriculture" by the Governor's Agriculture Net Receipts Working Group, 2003 (b35, f12); memorandum to Michael J. Schewel from Kendra Shifflett, Dept. of Planning and Budget, providing information on the cost of establishing the Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 27 June 2003 (b35, f14); Cabinet Meeting Notes, 2002-2005 (b37, f14-15); impact of drought on Virginia, 2002 (b39, f17); Education Policy Briefing-Office of the Goveror-Elect, Report of the Special Committee for Education, 2001 (b40, f6); Erskine's briefing book for European Marketing and Tourism Trip, June 2005 (b40, f8); meeting notes of the Virginia Agriculture and Forestry Export Strategy Task Force (b40, f13); transition overview materials, November 2001 (b41, f9); Health and Human Resources Policy Briefing, Office of the Governor-Elect, 2001 (b41, f14); Governor Warner's Trade Mission to Mexico briefing book, 9-12 November 2003 (b43, f17); notes on Phillip Morris relocating to Richmond, 2005 (b46, f12); and documents on the creation of the Warner Administration's Small Business Initiative, 2003-2004 (b47).
    The Events division is arranged in chronlogical order. These records document economic development events Erskine attended and includes copies of speeches/talking points/remarks he made.
    - Agency and Subject Files
      - Agency Head Meeting Agenda, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Avian Influenza, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Board of Accountancy, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Clarksville/Martinsville Governor's Follow Up Letters, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Commerce and Trade Executive Agreement, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Center, Clarksville, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Center, Martinsville, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Center, Smyth County, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Center, South Boston, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Department of Business Assistance, Small Business Legislation, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Department of Business Assistance, 2001-2004 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Department of Business Assistance, Waterford Furniture Makers, Lynchburg, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Department of Housing and Community Development, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Department of Labor and Industry, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Department of Minority Business Enterprise, Audit Report, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Dominion/IBEW Strike, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Department of Forestry, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - G.E. Financial Assurance, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Governor Baliles (Southwest and Southside) Initiatives Ideas, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Juvenile Treatment Facility, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Marion Composite ATP, Inc., 2002 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Department of Minority Business Enterprise, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Minority Business Enterprise-African American Businessmen Meeting, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Report: Big Expectations for Colleges and Universities Ahead, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Report: Building Biosciences-driven State and Regional Economies, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Report: Early Stage Capital in Spin-off Company Formation, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Focus Group Report HJ206 Task Force Meeting, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Report: Jump Starting Innovation, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Report: Research Results of Best Practices, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Scheduling, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Smyth County Strike Force, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Rural Entrepreneurship, 2003-2004 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Smyth County-Titan Wheel, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Southside Trip-Economic Task Force, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Southwet Virginia Tour, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Virginia Dept. Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2002-2003, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Virginia Executive Institute Aging Workshop, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Milk Commission, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Virginia Racing Commission, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Racing Commission, Best Practices Management, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Resources Authority, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Tourism Corporation, Executive Order, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2002-2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Virginia Tobacco Commmission, Agribusiness Committee, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Tobacco Commission, Southside Economic Development Committee, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Tobacco Commission, Southwest Economic Development, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Thank You Notes
      - 2002 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - 2003 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - 2004 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - 2005 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence-Chronological
      - 2002 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - 2003 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - 2004 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - 2005 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Special Projects
      - Activewear, 2002-2004 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Aerial-Patrick County, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Advantav, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Agency Budget Cuts, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Agriculture Day at the Virginia State Fair of Virginia, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Governor's Agriculture Net Receipts Working Group, 2003-2004 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Governor's Agriculture Net Receipts Working Group, 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Agriculture Profitability (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Agriculture Science Dinner at Mansion with Scientific Leaders (Proposal), 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Agriculture Summitt Action Team, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - America On Line (AOL), Call Center, 2002-2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Angel Investor Tax Credit, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Arlington County/Martinsville/Henry County, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Asia Trade Mission, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Aviation World's Fair, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Barboursville Vineyard Issue, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Baseball (Virginia), 2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Baseball Stadium Authority, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Basswood (American Tree), 2003 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Bass Outdoor World, Hampton, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Berry Hill Conference Center, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Berryville Signal Installation, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Best Management Practices Team-Boiler Pressure Vessel, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Best of Virginia Farms Cookbook (Fred Brown), 2004 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Biotech Legislation, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Biotech Commission Meeting, 2004-2005 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Virginia Biotechnology Initiative, Working Papers, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Biotechnology Initiative, Working Papers, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Bond Buyer Interview, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Botetourt County-Altec, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - A. Smith Bowman/Buffalo Trace Distillery, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC), 2003 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Broadband (Rural), 2003 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Buchanan County-Asbestos, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Buchanan County-Allegheny Energy, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Budget Meetings and Materials, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Buena Vista-ArvinMeritor, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Bush Industries Plant, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Business Constituent Outreach-J.H. Communication, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Cabela Proposal, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Cabinet Input Matrix-Secure Virginia, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Cabinet Meeting Notes, 2003-2005 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Cabinet Meeting Notes, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Cendant Corp., 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT)-Meeting on Private Equity, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT)-Reports, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT)-Land Use Study, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT)Roundtable, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commmission, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commmission, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Certified Capital Company Program (CAPCO), 2002 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Changing Planet, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Chronic Wasting Disease of Elk and Deer, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Columbia Flooring, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-Closing, 2002-2004 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-Report, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-Southwest and Southside Virginia, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-State Employee Assistance, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-Economic Strike Force, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-Economic Strike Force Annual Report, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-Decision Brief, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)(Governor's Economic Crisis Strike Force), Emporia/Greenville, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Coordinated Economic Relief Centers (CERC)-Economic Strike Force, Page and Green Counties, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Clarkton Bridge, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Commerce and Trade-General, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Commerce and Trade Initiative Matrix, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Commerce and Trade-Meetings with Governor Warner and Bill Leighty, 2003-2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Commerce and Trade Personnel, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Commercialization, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Congressional Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Constituent Affairs, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Continuing Education, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Cornell Tourism Study, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Crossroads Rural Entrepreneurial Institute, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Crystal City Real Estate, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Danville Workforce, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Delmarva Conservation Corridor Demonstration Program, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy-VITA Transition, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Executive Branch Departments, Overview, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Disater Recovery Task Force, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Disparity Study-Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Distressed Area Marketing Program, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-Economic Development and Impact, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-Report of Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-Food Nutrition and Health Institute, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-Forestry, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-The Economic Position of Virginia Agriculture, 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-Virginia Agriculture Summit, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Doubling Agricutlure Sales-Virginia Bioformatics Institute, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Doubling Agriculture Sales-Virginia Executive Institute Leadership Challenge, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Drake Extrusion, Inc., 2004 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Drought, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Drought-Letter to Nebraska Governor Mike Johanns, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Drought-Major Water Use Meeting, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Drought-Small Business Drought Relief Act, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Drought-Water Policy, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - E58-Mid-Atlantic Broadband, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Economic Bridege, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Economic Development Parternship, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Economic Job Numbers, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Education Policy Briefing-Office of the Goveror-Elect, Report of the Special Committee for Education, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Efficiency and Effectiveness in State Government, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - European Marketing and Tourism Trip, Briefing Book, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Executive Order 80, O-Ring Sprinklers in State-Owned Buildings, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Executive Order Review, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Export-Governor's Role, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Export Strategies-Agriculture and Forestry, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Virginia Agriculture and Forestry Export Strategy Task Force, 2004-2005 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - First Robotics, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Ford Motor Co., 2002 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Working Summit on Virginia Forest Industries, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Four Year Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Golf in Virginia-PGA Richmond Open, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Good News-Recommendations for Virginia Horse Racing, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Governor/NOVA CEO Dinner, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Governor's Conference on Economic Development, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Virginia Governor's Fellows Program, Preston Lloyd, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - General Policy, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - GreenTech-Charles Plageman, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - GRAB Machine, Shenandoah Engineering Services, Inc., 2002 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Growth Coalition-Urban Land Institute, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Harvard Business School Club, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Health and Human Resources Policy Briefing, Office of the Governor-Elect, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Higher Education Summit, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Higher Education-Research Summit, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Home Depot, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Homeland Security, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Homestead-State Rates, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - HJ 206 Task Force, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - House Joint Resolution 159-Board Reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Hungarian Technology Center, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Infineon, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Institute for Advanced Learning and Research, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - International Union of Painters, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Jamestown 2007 Steering Committee, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Jamestown 2007-Kent, England, 2004-2005 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Jamestown, 2007-Tourism, 2003-2004 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - Japan External Trade Organization (JETRO), 2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Jet Blue, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Jobs for Virginia-Alliance Texas, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Jobs for Virginia-Enhancing Our Strengths, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Jobs for Virginia-Pennsylvania's Economic Stimulus Package, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Jobs for Virginia-Ports of Virginia, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Jobs for Virginia-Tourism, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Kent, England-New Kent County, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Kia-Larry Austin, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Kilduff, Mark, Virginia Economic Development Partnership (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Kilmarnock-Industrial Access, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Kinetic Ventures, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Knauss Foods-Henry County, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Koch Industries Fuel Oil, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Knowledge Workers Meeting, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - L.F. Payne (Car Max), 2003 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Langley Wind Tunnel, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Leadership, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Town of Lebanon, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Legislation, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Legislation, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Legislation, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Manufacturing-Governor Warner's Trade Mission to Mexico Trip Book, 9-12 November 2003 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Manufacturing-Mission to Mexico, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Manufacturing-Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Manufacturing Needs, SJR 64 and 361, 2004-2005 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Manufacturing-An Advanced Proposal for the Commonwealth of Virginia, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Manufacturing Summit (Advance), 2004 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Governor's Working Summit on Advancing Manufacturing in Virginia, 2004-2005 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Marshall Plan for Southside Virginia, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 6)